<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Mark Fischer&#39;s Sports Blog</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Mark Fischer&#39;s Sports Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Were the 2021 Red Sox, Dare I Say, Lucky?</title>
      <link>/2022/05/01/were-the-2021-red-sox-dare-i-say-lucky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/05/01/were-the-2021-red-sox-dare-i-say-lucky/</guid>
      <description>Over the last four years, the Boston Red Sox have been one of the most inconsistent teams in the MLB. In 2018, they won the World Series against the Los Angeles Dodgers in a quick five game series. They followed that up with missing the playoffs entirely in 2019, going 84-78, and then finishing last in the AL East with a 24-36 record in 2020. Also during that span, the Red Sox fired Manager Alex Cora after the 2018 season and then re-hired him for the 2021 season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russell Wilson will win the Broncos a Super Bowl</title>
      <link>/2022/04/10/russell-wilson-will-win-the-broncos-a-super-bowl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2022/04/10/russell-wilson-will-win-the-broncos-a-super-bowl/</guid>
      <description>Man is it tough being a Broncos fan. Since Peyton Manning left after winning the Super Bowl in the 2015-2016 season, the Broncos have started 11 different QB’s with a combined record of 39-58. I also struggle to mention the fact of 14-straight losses to the repulsive team in Kansas City. The Broncos are a storied franchise with multiple Super Bowl wins and is home to many great players, so something has to fall in their favor, right?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
